ILGWU Research Department Records 5780/168
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Cone: Elmore Suit Docket, 1988-1992; Publication (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: General Docker U.S. Court of Appeals for the Fourth Circuit, Publication (Box 12, Folder 35)
    By Cone Mills Corp. April 13, 1992/June 26, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Civil Docket for Case #: 88-CV-3258, Publication (Box 12, Folder 35)
    By U.S. District Court District of South Carolina (Greenville). March 30, 1992. Item is in English.
- Cone: Company ESOP responses, 1989-1991; Publication (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Cone Press Statement, Publication (Box 12, Folder 36)
    October 1, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: SUBJECT: Your Right To Get Out Of The Union And Stop Union Dues, Publication (Box 12, Folder 36)
    By Sandra Barfield. November 14, 1990. Item is in English.
- Cone: Union ESOP responses, 1990-1991; Publication (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Cone Mills Corporation Election by Recipients of Nonperiodic (Lump Sum) Payments, Publication (Box 12, Folder 37)
    By Sharon V. Jennell. October 1990. Item is in English.
- Cone: Elmore Appeal, Publication (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: On Appeal from the United States District Court for the District of South Carolina, Publication (Box 12, Folder 38)
    By The United States Court of Appeals. Unknown Date/Publication. Item is in English.
- Cone: letters/leaflets 4-5/92, 1992; Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: A Message From The Employees Of Cone Mills To The Employees of Prudential Securities And J.P.Morgan & Co., Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). Item is in English.
  - Item 2: We Told Wall Street How We're Being Ripped Off!, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Item 3: We Took Cone On. And We WON!, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Item 4: When Cone Goes Publie, These Guys Will Be Millionares!, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Item 5: We're Fighting For What's Right!, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). Thursday, May 21/Friday, May 22 (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 6: The Union Times We're Standing Up For What's Right:, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
    By ACTWU Local 1391. June 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: What Will Workers Get When Cone Goes Public?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). Wednesday, April 22, Thursday, April 23, Friday, April 24 (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Millen, Georgia 1992 A Few Years Ago, Hundreds of Thomson Employees Worked here. No One Works Here Anymore., Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Item 9: Local 1584 Stands Up Strike!, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Item 10: Has Management Been A Little Upset This Week?, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). "negotiations on May 28." (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Standing Up For What's Right The Salisbury 19, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
    By Phil Cohen Organizer. "On May 18," (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 12: A Deal's A Deal: Cut Us In, Cone!, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). April 28, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Cone's Going Public. And We're Going Public Too!, Publication (Box 12, Folder 39)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). Unknown Date/Publicaton. Item is in English.
- Cone: ESOP settlement, 1983-1993; Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Today -- We Will Be Voting On A Proposal That Met All Our Goals:, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    Choice starts March 1 --- and have until April 12. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Mechanics, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Item 3: Cone and ACTWU, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    By Ernest Bennett. February 11, 1993. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Employees Left Holding the Bag, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    By Anne B. Fishe. May 20, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Cone Mills Workers Take Pension Protest to Greensboro Banks, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Item 6: Storming the Syndicate Desk, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    By Hal Lux. June 1, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Workers Want Their Share of Deal, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    By Rick Brooks. May 4, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Cone Union Takes Protest to Street, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    By Rick Brooks. May 15, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Cone Workers' Union Voice, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). March 22 (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Our Long Fight To End The ESOP Rip-Off: Now It's Time To Vote!, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
    By Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU). Thursday, February 11, Friday, February 12 (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The ESOP Cash Out Settlement, Publication (Box 12, Folder 40)
- Cone: Department of Labor complaint, 1989-1991; Publication (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Exhibit A, Publication (Box 12, Folder 41)
    By Edgar N. James. June 6, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Exhibit D, Publication (Box 12, Folder 41)
    By United States District Court for the District of South Carolina, Greenville Division. August 13, 1990, August 14, 1990, Filed. Item is in English.
- Cone: Morgan ADR update, 1992; Publication (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: News Release: Immediate JPMorgan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 42)
    By Richard A. Mahony (and Co.). April 26, 1991, October 17, 1991, May 22, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: 91 19 4850, Publication (Box 12, Folder 42)
    By Kenneth Lopian. September 3/20, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Sec Filings in 1990 Reveal Morgan Stockpiling New South African ADR Registrations, Publication (Box 12, Folder 42)
    January 1991. Item is in English.
- J.P. Morgan 4/91, 1991; Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: J.P. Morgan Ends South Africa ADR Processing Work, Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
    By Fred R. Bleakley. Monday, April 29, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Palo Alto Satisfied with Bank, Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
    By Abbie Jones. Wednesday, August 8, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Massachusetts GO Syndicate Candidate Faces Call for Probe On South Africa Link, Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
    By Ted Hampton. Friday, April 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: J.P. Morgan Gets Left Out But the Bank Says It's a Cheap Shot, Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
    By Robert Duffy. April 22, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Sever Ties, Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
    By Ren Norton. Friday, April 5, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: J.P. Morgan Ends South Africa ADR Processing Work, Publication (Box 12, Folder 43)
- Cone: Floor Offset law, 1987-1991; Publication (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Floor-Offset Plan Risks Eyed, Publication (Box 12, Folder 44)
    By Nicky Robertshaw. November 2, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: U.S. Seeks to Curb ESOP Use, Publication (Box 12, Folder 44)
    By Joel Chernoff. March 9, 1987. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Legislative History House Report No. 100-391(1), Publication (Box 12, Folder 44)
    (Unknown Date/Publication). Item is in English.
  - Item 4: United States Code 1988 Edition Title 29--Labor, Publication (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Item 5: C'mon Cone, Come Clean! Let's End The ESOP Rip-Off, Publication (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Item 6: United States Code Annotated Title 29 Labor, Publication (Box 12, Folder 44)
    1990 Culmulative Annual Pocket Part. Item is in English.
- Cone: SACTWU Letter to Trogdon 3/20, 1991; Publication (Box 12, Folder 45)
- Cone: Press Releases/Fact Sheets, Publication (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: For Immediate Release: Cone Mills Employees to Protest Company's June Public Offering as May 18th Contract Deadline Looms, Publication (Box 12, Folder 46)
    By Micheal Zucker. May 14, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: News Release For Immediate Release ACTWU Wins 5.6 Percent Wage-Benefit Increase at Cone Mills In Largest Package Seen Among Major Textile Companies, Publication (Box 12, Folder 46)
    By Kim Klesty. Thursday May 30, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Campaign to Reform Cone Mills ESOP Continues Cone Mills Warriors to Hold Demonstration In Front of Company Headquarters, File Complaint with U.S. Department of Labor, Publication (Box 12, Folder 46)
    By Kim Klesty, Michael Zucker. Embargoed Until June 6, 1991. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: For Release: Wednesday A.M. Cone Mills Corporation Employees To File Suit Against Company Pension and Employee Stock Ownership Plans at Federal District Courthouse Wednesday. Rally to be Held., Publication (Box 12, Folder 46)
    By Ernest Bennerr/Carol Sheerer, Michael Zucker. June 26, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Fact Sheet, Publication (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Item 6: Fact Sheet on the Cone Mills Employee Stock Ownership Plan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 46)
    1983/1984. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: For Immediate Release Cone Mills Workers Lauch Multi-State Campaign to Reform Employee Stock Ownership Plan--Protests to be Held at Company Manufacturing Facilities Next Monday, Publication (Box 12, Folder 46)
    By Ernest Bennett, Denise Mitchell, Michael Zucker. Saptember 27, 1990. Item is in English.
- Cone: Hattis v. Baynes, 1990-1991; Publication (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Civil Action No., Publication (Box 12, Folder 47)
    By The United States District Court for the Middle District of North Carolina Greensboro Division. June 25, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Exhibit E 1st Case of Level 1 Printed in Full Format, Publication (Box 12, Folder 47)
    October 3, 1980. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Union Uses Media to Wage Battle With Firms, Publication (Box 12, Folder 47)
    By Kathryn Hopper. Unknown Date/Publication. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: ACTWU Sues Cone Mills To Obtain Pension Information, Publication (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Item 5: Initial Pretrial Stipulations and Order, Publication (Box 12, Folder 47)
    By Smith Patternson. October 1, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Defendants' First Request for Production of Documents to Plaintiffs, Publication (Box 12, Folder 47)
    By Robert J. Lawing. September 20th, 1990. Item is in English.
- Cone: Labor Department complaint, 6 June 1991, Publication (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Civil Action No. 1:86-937-8 O R D E R, Publication (Box 12, Folder 48)
    By Ann A. Birch. November 27, 1989. Item is in English.
- Morgan: Shareholder reso/correspondence, Publication (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Statement of Support for Stockholder Proposal Relating to South Africa, Publication (Box 12, Folder 49)
- Morgan: letters, 1990-1991; Publication (Box 12, Folder 50)
- Morgan: Corporate letters to Bill P., 1991; Publication (Box 12, Folder 51)
- Government Letters to Bill Patterson, 1991; Publication (Box 12, Folder 52)
- ICCR Resolutions: 1991 Morgan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Sharholder Resolution for 1991 Annual Meetings of US Banks, Publication (Box 12, Folder 53)
    January 29, 1991. Item is in English.
- City Hearing: Press Materials, 1990; Publication (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Probe May Cost Bank Milllions, Publication (Box 12, Folder 54)
    By Rebecca Smith. Wednesday, August 8, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Anglo American Corporation of South America LTD/ADR/, Publication (Box 12, Folder 54)
    By Robert E. Murray. July 13/18, 1990. Item is in English.
- Morgan: Shareholder Activities, Publication (Box 12, Folder 55)
- Harris v. Baynes II, 1990; Publication (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Memorandum in Support of Plaintiffs' Motion for Judgement on the Pleadings, Publication (Box 12, Folder 56)
    By Jonathan R. Harkavy, Edgar N. James. November 6, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Plaintiffs' Motion for Judgement on the Pleadings, Publication (Box 12, Folder 56)
    By Edgar N. James. November 5, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: 3rd Letter of Level 1 Printed in Full Format, Publication (Box 12, Folder 56)
    By Jeffery N. Clayton. July 21, 1982. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: O-R-D-E-R 2:90CV00319, Publication (Box 12, Folder 56)
    By United States Magistrate. November 29, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Plaintiffs' Opposition to Defendants' Motion for Costs and Attorneys' Fees, Publication (Box 12, Folder 56)
    By Jonathan R. Harkavy. March 1, 1991. Item is in English.
- Cone: Campaign Press 1992, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Storming the Syndicate Desk, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Item 2: Cone Mills May Be One of the Bargain Stocks Created by Saturation of Initial Public Offerings Heard on the Street, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By George Anders. Unknown Date/Publication. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Cone Mills Workers OK Contract, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By Pamela Moore. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Workers in ESOP "We're Screwed", Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By Anne B. Fisher. June 29, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: IPO Riles Union Workers, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By Christine Philip. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Workers Want Their Share of Deal, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Item 7: Cone May Face Liability of $49 Mil in ESOP Case, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Item 8: Union Stages One-Day Strike At Cone Mills Plant, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By Dow Jones. May 19? (Unknown Year). Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Cone Mills Employees Protest Company's Upcoming Stock Deal, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By Aaron Pressman. May 18, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Cone Workers Strike Again, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Item 11: Information Packet: Cone Mills Stock Offering Protest, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By Michael Zucker. May 14, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Current Developments, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By DLR. June 10, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Stock Proposal Angers Cone Mills Workers, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    Wednesday, May 27, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Cone Mills Workers Pleading Their Case in Wall Street Offices, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Item 15: Hundreds Apply for Jobs at Cone Mills, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By Mark Wineka. May 21/22, 1992. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Cone Announces Wage Increase, Retirement Plan, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By Charles L. Warner. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: ACTW Holds Protest at Cone, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Item 18: Cone to Trim Debt with Sale of Stock, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By Rick Brooks. Unknown Date/Publication. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Stock Market Looks Good to Cone Mills, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Item 20: Cone Mills Returns to Profitablity, Publication (Box 12, Folder 57)
    By Steve Farnsworth. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
- Cone Mills: Articles - originals, 1992; Publication (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Lichto: Clips, 1988, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Union and Plant Owner Tangle in Labor Hearing, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Mardy Jackson. Wednesday, August 31, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Two Labor Demonstrations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Kenneth C. Crowe. Friday, May 6, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: EEOC Discrimination Charges Filed Against the S. Lichtenberg Company, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Nancy Peckenham. December 17-23, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Jackson's Success Propels Activists, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    By Marcha Mercer. June 26, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: A Different Union Army Invades the South, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    May 4-10, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: JLC Joins National ACTWU Campaign in Support of S. Lichtenberg & Co. Workers, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    Falls 1988 Issue. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: News Letter, Publication (Box 13, Folder 1)
    December, 1988. Item is in English.
- Lichto: Clips, 1989, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Jackson Urges Solidarity, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Thursday, January 18, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Labor Board Ruling Favors Union Effort, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Thursday, October 19, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Samson And Delila: Slavery In Georgia, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    May 4 - 10, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Effort to Unionize Hints of Old South, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Billy Bowles. Monday, April 17, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Delegates Pledge Help for Embattled Unions, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    February 23, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Metro Detroit Supports Struggle of Southern Textile Workers, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    May 18,1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Banjamin L. Hooks and Georgia NAACP State Conference President Call for Support of Textile Workers, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    March 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: 'We're Not Grasshoppers, We're Giants', Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Caucus Urges Probe Into Unfairness, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Juanita Bratcher. Tuesday, September 19, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Union Representatives Please with Support of Black Caucus, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Beth Harrison. Friday, September 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Black Caucus Backs Union, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 12: Black Caucus Aids ACTWU Members in Georgia, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    September 30, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Drapery Firm Probe Sought, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Thursday, September 14, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Letters to the Editor, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Editor of The True Citizen. Wednesday, February 22, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Labor Dispute Becoming Racial Explotation Issue, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Jim Wooten. July 12, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Bitter War for Better Wages, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Marilyn Milloy. Monday, July 10, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: OSHA Fines Owner of 2 Factories, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Chris Burritt. Friday, April 21, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Southern Clothing Workers Fight for Decent Contract, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Aurthur Hoover. December, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Union Charges South Gworgia Company Practices Racism, Discrimination, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    February 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Fanfare Salutes Keyville's Struggle And King's Dream, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    January 18, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: More Than They're Worth, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Wednesday. February 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: EEOC Discrimination Charges Filed Against The S. Lichtenberg Company, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    January 20, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: A Right to Work With Dignity, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Judy Mann. Friday, July 28, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: K Mart Stockholders Hear Worker Plea, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Denise L. Smith. Wednesday, May 24, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 25: Judge Dismisses Protests Against Union Organizing, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Shelia M. Poole. Saturday, July 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Lichtenberg to Fight Charge 61 Unfairly Dismissed, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Shelia M. Poole. Wednesday, June 28, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: Labor Board Oks Union At Two Drapery Factories, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Shelia Poole. Wednesday, October 18, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 28: S. Lichtenberg Workers Given Union Approval By National Labor Board, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Beth Harrison. Tuesday, October17, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: Textile Strength Poetry of Struggle in Rural Georgia, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Sharon Roberson and Barbara Hines Lewis. June 20, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 30: S. Lichenberg and Company: Searching for Justice at Samsons and Delila, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Prepared by the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. April 15, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 31: Unionists Celebrate Dr. King, Push for Nationwide Holiday, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Magda Lynn Seymour. January 22, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 32: OSHA Fines Owner of 2 Factories, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 33: S. Lichtenberg Workers, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Item 34: Georgia Textile Fight Has Racial Overtones, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Billy Bowles. April 23, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 35: Samsons and Delila: Struggle in the New South, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Richard L. Trumka. November-December, 1989. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Jesse Jackson Supports Georgia Textile Workers, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Nancy Peckenham. January 29, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 37: Textile Firm Hit With Suit, Publication (Box 13, Folder 2)
    By Beth Harrison. Wednesday, February 7, 1990. Item is in English.
- Lichto: Jewish resources, NATC/NY, 1988; Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Consultation on Conscience -- April 9 - 11, 1989, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    November 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: "The Religious Action Center is an Effective Answer to Those Who Dent the Responsibilities of Religion for Correcting Injustice." -President John F. Kennedy December 1, 1962, Publication (Box 13, Folder 3)
    By Alexander M. Schindler. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
- Worker Letters to AMES, 1988-1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Union Versus Lichentenberg During Market, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    By Larry Leventhal. May 9, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Two Labor Demonstrations, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Lichtenberg Business Goes On Despite Disruption By Union, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
    By Donna Boyle Schwartz. May 16, 1988. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Letters to J.C. Penney Chairman William B. Howell, Publication (Box 13, Folder 4)
- S. Lichtenberg - NY Clips, 1988; Publication (Box 13, Folder 5)
- K-mart: Communications, 1988-1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Civil Rights Journal, Publication (Box 13, Folder 6)
    By Benjamin F. Chavis, Jr. May 6-12, 1989. Item is in English.
- Lichto: JC Penney Campaign, 1989-1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Penney's Target of Labor Activists, Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
    March 30, 1990. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Buy Out Curtains and Drapes! (Made by S. Lichtenberg), Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
    By Harold Galloway and Danny DeLaigle. Unknown Date. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Attention JCPenney Employees, Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: 40 Seek Talks With Penney Official Over Problems With Textile Firm, Publication (Box 13, Folder 7)
    By Stephanie Ward. Friday, March 30, 1990. Item is in English.
- Responses FR. Stores, 1989-1990; Publication (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Responses from Customers, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Jamesway Correspondence, 1989; Publication (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Bill S-J Speech, Publication (Box 13, Folder 11)